Guide to the Walter Boychuk Photographs 1912-1961
Oregon Historical Society, Research Library
- Prints from original negatives, 1918-1961; Group 2
  - Other locations, 1919-1950; Series C
    - Nevada - Virginia City, circa 1940 (Box-folder 6/31)
      Includes St. Mary's of the Mountain church, the Storey Company courthouse, and Piper's Opera House.
    - Nevada - Virginia City cemetery, circa 1940 (Box-folder 6/32)
    - Nevada - Virginia City - Residences, circa 1940 (Box-folder 6/33)
      Includes the John Bauer residence, Savage Mansion, and "The Castle."
    - Washington - Long Beach, 1938 (Box-folder 7/1)
      Includes images of fishing boats, clam digging, and Anna Boychuk.
    - Washington - Maryhill Museum, 1937 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - Washington - Mary's Corner, John R. Jackson residence, circa 1930 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - Washington - Mount Adams, circa 1920 (Box-folder 7/4-5)
      Includes image of the Mazamas Glacier, a view from Hood River, and Cascade Locks with Mount Adams in the background.
    - Washington - Mount Baker, circa 1950 (Box-folder 7/6)
      Includes image(s) of Anna Boychuk.
    - Washington - Mount Rainier, 1919 (Box-folder 7/7)
      Includes images of a Mazamas outing and Walter Boychuk.
    - Washington - Mount Rainier glaciers, 1919 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - Washington - Mount Rainier lookout, 1919 (Box-folder 7/9)
    - Washington - Mount St. Helens from Spirit Lake, circa 1930 (Box-folder 7/10)
    - Washington - Mount Shuksan, circa 1945 (Box-folder 7/11)
    - Washington - North Head, circa 1930 (Box-folder 7/12)
    - Washington - Olympia, circa 1935 (Box-folder 7/13)
      Includes image of the Washington state capitol building.
    - Washington - Seattle, circa 1935 (Box-folder 7/14)
      Includes images of Volunteer Park and the Seattle Art Museum.
    - Washington - Skamania, circa 1930 (Box-folder 7/15)
    - Washington - Skamania County - Fort Rains, circa 1930 (Box-folder 7/16)
    - Washington - Stonehenge, 1937 August 29 (Box-folder 7/17)
    - Washington - Tatoosh Range from Mount Rainier, 1919 (Box-folder 7/18)
    - Washington - Vancouver Apple Tree, circa 1930 (Box-folder 7/19)
    - Washington - Vancouver - Port Commission Dock, circa 1930 (Box-folder 7/20)
      Includes image of the grain elevator.
    - Washington - Whidby Island, 1938 (Box-folder 7/21)
    - Wyoming - Cody, 1919 (Box-folder 7/22)
      Includes images of Walter Boychuk and relating to Prisma Movies.
  - Portraits, 1930-1961; Series D
    - Men, 1930-1960; Subseries 1
      - Adolph Aschoff, 1931 (Box-folder 7/23)
      - John G. Bacher, circa 1950 (Box-folder 7/24)
      - Steffan Bercs, 1953 August 13 (Box-folder 7/25)
      - Ernest Bloch, 1957 February 20 (Box-folder 7/26)
      - Ambrose Brownell, 1949 October 15 (Box-folder 7/27)
      - Asahel Nesmith Bush, 1947 February 20 (Box-folder 7/28)
      - Adam Cartozian, 1956 August 2 (Box-folder 7/29)
      - Hamilton Corbett, 1959 August 18 (Box-folder 7/30)
      - Rev. Benjamin Dagwell, 1950 June 20 (Box-folder 7/31)
      - Allen H. Eaton, 1952 July 10 (Box-folder 7/32)
      - Anthony Ewer, circa 1935 (Box-folder 7/33)
      - James Alger Fee, 1938 March 9 (Box-folder 7/34)
      - Austin Flegel, 1950 February 20 (Box-folder 7/35)
      - William Galvani, circa 1945 (Box-folder 7/36)
      - J. J. Guillan, 1959 July 16 (Box-folder 7/37)
      - W. Hancock, 1952 April 24 (Box-folder 7/38)
      - Ben H. Hazen, 1950 April 11 (Box-folder 7/39)
      - Edward R. Heilig, 1952 December 19 (Box-folder 7/40)
      - Robert D. Holmes, 1958 July 31 (Box-folder 7/41)
      - W. H. (Ted) Holmes, 1949 September 4 (Box-folder 7/42)
      - Jacob Kanzler, circa 1950 (Box-folder 7/43)
      - Clyde Leon Keller, 1948 March 5 (Box-folder 7/44)
      - Francis Lambert, 1958 July 9 (Box-folder 7/45-46)
      - Ben Hur Lampman, circa 1920, 1949 March 29 (Box-folder 7/47)
      - Fletcher Linn, 1951 May 3 (Box-folder 7/48)
      - E. B. MacNaughton, 1950 May 2 (Box-folder 8/1)
      - Charles H. Manlove, 1943 May 17 (Box-folder 8/2)
      - Phil Melochan, 1951 May 18 (Box-folder 8/3)
      - Dent Mowry, circa 1936 (Box-folder 8/4)
      - Audie Murphy, circa 1950 (Box-folder 8/5)
      - Morgan S. Odell, 1955 September 20 (Box-folder 8/6)
      - Robert J. Oppenheimer, 1955 May 1 (Box-folder 8/7)
      - Paul Patterson, 1954 February 8, 1956 January 23 (Box-folder 8/8)
      - Theodore Pentland, 1941 (Box-folder 8/9)
      - Fred Peterson, 1952 July 10 (Box-folder 8/10)
      - Paul Raver, 1960 March 23 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - J. J. Rosenberg, 1949 November 11 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - James Buchanan Russell, circa 1950 (Box-folder 8/13)
      - T. H. Schoene, 1952 January 3 (Box-folder 8/14)
      - Terry D. Schrunk, 1950 July 21 (Box-folder 8/15)
      - Elmo Smith, 1956 February 9 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - MacCormac Snow, 1949 August 11 (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Gus J. Solomon, 1959 April 11 (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Charles Sprague, 1942 February 23 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Glen Stanton, 1959 August 26 (Box-folder 8/20)
      - Lowell Thomas, 1947 March 18 (Box-folder 8/21)
      - Henry Thiele, 1949 June 29 (Box-folder 8/22)
      - Norman Thomas, 1950 February 28 (Box-folder 8/23)
    - Women, 1930-1961; Subseries 2
      - Adrianna Katherine Barclay, 1933 (Box-folder 8/24)
      - Mrs. William Cody, circa 1917 (Box-folder 8/25)
        Mrs. William Cody was the wife of Buffalo Bill Cody.
      - Mrs. Theron Fells, 1951 June 21 (Box-folder 8/26)
      - Claire Haney, circa 1950 (Box-folder 8/27)
      - Mary Haney, 1961 December 5 (Box-folder 8/28)
      - Matilda Howard, circa 1930 (Box-folder 8/29)
        Also known as Grandma Graham Howard.
      - Thelma Howard, circa 1930 (Box-folder 8/30)
        Granddaughter of Grandma Graham Howard.
      - Edna Levy Frank Holmes, 1950 October 5 (Box-folder 8/31)
      - Maria Foster Clapton Jackson, 1947 September 4 (Box-folder 8/32)
      - Mary Lyman Andrews Ladd, circa 1950 (Box-folder 8/33)
      - Mrs. Jason Malarkey, 1950 April 19 (Box-folder 8/34)
      - Mrs. Albert Powers, 1959 March 20 (Box-folder 8/35)
      - Mrs. Paul Raver, 1950 April 7 (Box-folder 8/36)
      - Mrs. Gus J. Solomon, 1959 April 11 (Box-folder 8/37)
    - Groups, 1951-1952; Subseries 3
      - Walter Boychuk, Allen Eaton, Walter H. Evans, and Fletcher Linn, 1952 (Box-folder 8/38)
      - George W. Dunn, Ella Dunn Rice, and Fletcher Linn with ancient Indian grinding stones, 1951 September 21 (Box-folder 8/39)
  - Ships and transportation, 1930-1940; Series E
    - Ships, circa 1935 (Box-folder 8/40)
    - Ships - Elizabeth Bakke, circa 1939-1940 (Box-folder 8/41)
    - Ships - Unidentified ship flying Nazi flag, circa 1930 (Box-folder 8/42)
    - Ships - Military - Battleships, 1937 (Box-folder 8/43)
    - Ships - Military - USS Astoria, 1937 (Box-folder 8/44)
    - Ships - Military - USS Chicago, circa 1935 (Box-folder 8/45)
    - Ships - Military - USS Houston, 1934 (Box-folder 8/46)
      President Franklin Delano Roosevelt on board.
    - Ships - Military - USS Minneapolis, 1937 (Box-folder 8/47)
    - Ships - Military - USS Oregon, 1912 (Box-folder 8/48)
    - Ships - Military - USS Oregon, 1939 (Box-folder 8/49)
    - Ships - Military - USS Relief, 1937 (Box-folder 8/50)
    - Ships - Sailing - Old schooner, Portland Harbor, circa 1935 (Box-folder 8/51)
    - Ships - Sailing - Taisei Maru, 1930 (Box-folder 8/52)
    - Ships - Sailing - USS Constitution, 1933 (Box-folder 8/53)
    - Transportation - Aviation - Russian airplane, 1937 (Box-folder 8/54)
  - Other subjects, 1918-1940; Series F
    - Agriculture - Buildings - Deserted house, circa 1935 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - Agriculture - Cranberry harvest, circa 1940 (Box-folder 9/2)
      Includes image of Anna Boychuk.
    - Agriculture - Hops dryer, circa 1935 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - Agriculture - Sheep, circa 1940 (Box-folder 9/4)
    - Eclipse of the sun, 1918 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - Fishing, circa 1935 (Box-folder 9/6)
    - Nature studies, circa 1935 (Box-folder 9/7)
      Includes swans, geese, "snow birds," and humming birds.
    - Natures studies - Flowers, circa 1935 (Box-folder 9/8)
      Includes magnophilla, balsam orchiza, trillium, daphne, and dogwood.
    - Nature studies - Plants, circa 1935 (Box-folder 9/9)
      Includes lewisii rediviva, balsam, and bear grass.
    - Nature studies - Trees, circa 1935 (Box-folder 9/10)
      Includes magnolia, mistletoe-oak, cherry, chinquapin, vine maple, and apple.
    - Scenic views, circa 1935 (Box-folder 9/11)
      Includes birches and jonquilla, woodland road.
    - Scenic views with people, circa 1925 (Box-folder 9/12)
      Woodland trail with female hiker, "Homeward Bound."
  - Copy work, 1915-1959; Series G
    - Bradford Island, circa 1925 (Box-folder 9/13)
    - Old Hoffman Cabin, Originally taken in 1853; copy print undated (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
    - Mitchell's Tunnel, circa 1915 (Box-folder 9/14)
    - Inauguration of Elisha P. Ferry as first governor of Washington state, Originally taken 1889 November 18; copy print made 1927 (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
    - Abraham Lincoln and family, Originally taken circa 1860; copy undated (Box-folder 9/15)
    - Pope John XXII, 1959 March 25 (Box-folder 9/16)
    - Portland Hotel, Originally taken 1890; copy undated (Box-folder 9/17)
    - Terwilliger School, Originally taken circa 1900; copy undated (Box-folder 9/18)
    - Portland flood, Originally taken 1890; copy undated (Box-folder 9/19)
    - Portland harbor, Originally taken 1895; copy undated (Box-folder 9/20)
    - Skiing, 1932 February 21 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Historic American Building Survey, 1930-1951; Series H
    - Residences, Subseries 1
      - Applegate, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 9/22)
        Home of Kaspar Kubli.
      - Ashland, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 9/23)
        Homes of Hugh Barron, Patrick Dunn, and W. C. Meyer.
      - Central Point, undated (Box-folder 9/24)
        Home of Thomas Fletcher Beall
      - Champoeg, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 9/25)
        Home of Robert Newell.
      - Eugene, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 9/26)
        Homes of Prior Blair, Dr. Chapman, Thomas Condon, and J. J. Walton, as well as of Masterson Farm.
      - Gold Hill, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 9/27)
        Home of David Birdseye.
      - Hubbard, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 9/28)
        Stauffer family home.
      - Jacksonville, circa 1935 (Box-folder 9/29)
        Homes of Applegate family, C. C. Beekman, John Bilger, Peter Britt, and William Bybee.
      - Jacksonville, circa 1935 (Box-folder 9/30)
        Homes of James Cardwell, Benjamin Franklin Dowell, Michael Hanley, Herman Helm, Herbert Hanna, and William Hoffman.
      - Jacksonville, circa 1935 (Box-folder 9/31)
        Homes of Henry Klippel, Kasper Kubli, and David Linn.
      - Jacksonville, circa 1935 (Box-folder 9/32)
        Homes of James McCurty, J. N. Y. Miller, Max Mueller, Jerry Nunan, John Orth, P. P. Prim, Thomas G. Reams, and John E. Ross.
      - Medford, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 9/33)
        Home of Gore family.
      - Milwaukie, 1930 (Box-folder 9/34)
        Home of Seth Llewelyn.
      - Oregon City, 1930 (Box-folder 9/35)
        Homes of J. C. Ainsworth, John Barclay, William Livingston Holmes ("Rose far,"), and Norton McCarver.
      - Oregon City, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 9/36)
        Home of John McLoughlin.
      - Portland, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 9/37)
        Home of Winslow Corbett.
      - Portland, circa 1935 (Box-folder 9/38)
        Home of Jacob Kramm.
      - Portland, circa 1945 (Box-folder 9/39)
        Home of John Kern.
      - Reedville, 1930 (Box-folder 9/40)
        Home of Simon G. Reed.
      - Silverton, undated (Box-folder 9/41)
        Home of Homer Davenport.
      - Salem, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 9/42)
        Home of E. N. Cook.
      - Scotts Valley, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 9/43)
        Home of John Letsom.
      - Talent, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 9/44)
        Home of E. K. Anderson.
      - Yoncalla, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 9/45)
        Home of Charles Applegate.
    - Buildings, Subseries 2
      - Crawfordsville Mill, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 10/1)
      - Dalles - Fort Dalles, circa 1945 (Box-folder 10/2)
      - Dayton - Block House, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Eagle Point - Brown Warehouse, circa 1945 (Box-folder 10/4)
      - Jacksonville - Business buildings, circa 1935 (Box-folder 10/5)
        Includes the C. C. Beekman Bank. Brunner Building, I.O.O.F. Building, Wes Kahler's Law Office, J. W. Opp Quartz Mill, Patrick Ryan Store, and the U.S. Hotel.
      - Jacksonville - Churches, circa 1935 (Box-folder 10/6)
        Includes the Catholic church and the Presbyterian church.
      - Jacksonville - Public buildings, circa 1935 (Box-folder 10/7)
        Includes city hall, Masonic building, fire station, and museum.
      - Jacksonville - Maps, circa 1935 (Box-folder 10/8)
      - New Era Church, circa 1940 (Box-folder 10/9)
      - Parkersville Hotel, 1941 March 30 (Box-folder 10/10)
      - Pleasant Grove Church, 1941 March 31 (Box-folder 10/11)
      - Portland - Pioneer Post Office, circa 1935 (Box-folder 10/12)
      - Rock Point - Stage Coach House, 1951 September 29 (Box-folder 10/13)
      - Salem - Old Court House, 1951 September 29 (Box-folder 10/14)
      - Salem - Old State Capitol, circa 1931-1935 (Box-folder 10/15)
      - Scio - Providence Church, 1941 March 30 (Box-folder 10/16)
      - Silverton - Liberal University, circa 1940 (Box-folder 10/17)
      - St. Louis - Catholic church, circa 1940 (Box-folder 10/18)
      - St. Paul - Catholic church, circa 1940 (Box-folder 10/19)
      - Wolf Creek Tavern, circa 1940 (Box-folder 10/20)
  - Golden Gate International Exposition, 1940; Series I
    - Berkeley, Calif., 1940 (Box-folder 10/21)
    - Buildings, 1940 (Box-folder 10/22)
      Includes locations in Salinas Valley, Monterey, and Palo Alto, Calif.
    - San Francisco, 1940 (Box-folder 10/23)
    - San Francisco - Golden Gate International Exposition, 1940 (Box-folder 10/24)
    - San Francisco - Golden Gate International Exposition sculptures, 1940 (Box-folder 10/25)
    - Carmel, Calif., 1940 (Box-folder 10/26)
    - California missions, 1940 (Box-folder 10/27)
      Includes Santa Barbara and San Miguel.
    - California - Scenes, 1940 (Box-folder 10/28)
      Includes coast and redwoods.
- Vintage prints, 1922-1957; Group 2
  - Oregon locations, 1930-1957; Series A
    - Lost Creek Meadows, undated (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
      Photographed titled by Boychuk, "Valley of Contentment, Oregon."
    - Milwaukie - Llewellyn residence, 1930 (Box-folder 10/29)
    - Oregon City - McLaughlin residence, circa 1930-1931 (Box-folder 10/30)
    - Portland - Temple Beth Israel Synagogue, undated (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
    - Portland - St. Johns Bridge, circa 1936 (Box-folder 10/31)
    - Portland - Firefighting, 1933 August 1 (Box-folder 10/32)
    - Portland - Mary Mallory studio, circa 1936 (Box-folder 10/33)
    - Portland - Harry A. Roberts residence, circa 1936 (Box-folder 10/34)
    - Portland - St. Thomas More church, 1940 September 22 (Box-folder 10/35)
    - Portland - University Club, 1952 (Box-folder 10/36)
    - Eastern Oregon - Alvord Ranch, circa 1945 (Box-folder 10/37)
  - Portraits, 1922-1957; Series B
    - Men - George J. Annola, circa 1957 (Box-folder 10/38)
    - Men - Adolph Aschoff, 1930 May 17 (Box-folder 10/39)
    - Men - Ernest Bloch, 1957 February 20 (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
    - Men - Hamilton Corbett, 1959 August 18 (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
    - Men - Dr. Ira N. Gabrielson, undated (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
    - Men - Jesse B. Hornung, undated (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
    - Men - Jacques Gershkovitz, circa 1950 (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
    - Men - Francis Lambert, 1952 March 6 (Box-folder 10/40)
    - Men - Ben Hur Lampman, 1944 March 29 (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
    - Men - Fletcher Linn, 1951 May 3 (Box-folder 10/41)
    - Men - Dent Mowry, circa 1936 (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
    - Men - Dr. Morgan S. Odell, 1955 September 20 (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
    - Men - David Robinson, 1950 July 10 (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
    - Women - Maria Foster Clapton Jackson, 1947 September 4 (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
    - Women - Anne Kerr, 1928 (Box-folder 10/42)
    - Women - Mrs. Duncan Shields, 1928 July 1 (Box-folder 10/43)
    - Women - Unidentified, circa 1936 (Box-folder 10/44)
    - Women - Unidentified, undated (Box-folder Oversize B/1)
    - Group - Mazamas, Three Sisters outing, 1922 (Box-folder 10/45)
    - Group - George W. Dunn, Ella Dunn Rice, and Fletcher Linn, 1951 (Box-folder 10/46)
    - Group - Tom Young family, 1957 (Box-folder 10/47)
    - Group - Theater - Junior Pageant, 1928 (Box-folder 10/48)
      Depicts Ruby Asquith and Claire Leonard as Beauty and the Beast.
  - Historic American Buildings Survey, 1930-1951; Series C
    - Oregon
      - Anlauf - Mt. House Hotel, undated (Box-folder 11/1)
      - Applegate, undated (Box-folder 11/2)
        Includes homes of Peter Applegate and Kasper Kubli.
      - Ashland, undated (Box-folder 11/3)
        Includes homes of H. F. Barron, Hugh Barron, W. C. Meyer, and Patrick and Mary M. Dunn.
      - Aurora - Home of Dr. Keil, undated (Box-folder 11/4)
      - Central Point - Thomas F. Beall home, undated (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Champoeg - Robert Newell home, undated (Box-folder 11/6)
      - The Dalles - Fort Dalles, undated (Box-folder 11/7)
      - Dayton - Block House, undated (Box-folder 11/8)
      - Eagle Point - George Brown & Sons warehouse, undated (Box-folder 11/9)
      - Eugene, undated (Box-folder 11/10)
        Includes homes of Prior Brown, D. Bristow, Thomas Condon, W. A. Masterson, and J. J. Walton.
      - Gold Hill - Chauvner family home, undated (Box-folder 11/11)
      - Grants Pass - David N. Birdseye home, undated (Box-folder 11/12)
      - Hubbard - Stauffer family home, undated (Box-folder 11/13)
      - Jacksonville - Business buildings, undated (Box-folder 11/14)
        Includes Beekman Bank, Brunner Building, City Hall, Wes Kohler Law Office, McCully Building, Opp Quartz Mill, and the U.S. Hotel.
      - Jacksonville - Public buildings, undated (Box-folder 11/16)
        Includes Jacksonville Museum, Masonic building, and Old Fire Bell.
      - Jacksonville - Residences, undated (Box-folder 11/17)
        Homes of J. C. Ainsworth, the Armstrong family, Cornelius C. Beekman, John Bilger, Peter Britt, and William Bybee.
      - Jacksonville - Residences, undated (Box-folder 11/18)
        Homes of the Cardwell family, Benjamin Franklin Dowell, the Dox family, Michael Hanley, Herbert H. Hanna, the Harbaugh family, William Hoffman, and Herman Holm.
      - Jacksonville - Residences, undated (Box-folder 12/1)
        Homes of the Jacobs family, Henry Klipple, Kasper Kubli, the Levy family, David Linn, and the Love family.
      - Jacksonville - Residences, undated (Box-folder 12/2)
        Homes of James Mason McCully, J. N. T. Miller, Max Mueller, Jerry Numan, John Orth, Pain Page Prim, the Pape family, Thomas G. Reames, and John E. Ross.
      - Medford, undated (Box-folder 12/3)
        Homes of the Gore and Vandyke families.
      - Milwaukie - Seth Llewellyn home, undated (Box-folder 12/4)
      - Newburg - John Henry Minthorn home, undated (Box-folder 12/5)
      - Oregon City, undated (Box-folder 12/6)
        Homes of Forbes Barclay, William Livingston Holmes, Norton McCarver, and John McLoughlin.
      - Portland, undated (Box-folder 12/7)
        Includes homes of Henry Winslow Corbett and John Kern, Front Street, and Skidmore Fountain.
      - Reedville - Simon G. Reed home, undated (Box-folder 12/8)
      - Riddle - Abner Riddle home, undated (Box-folder 12/9)
      - Rock Point - Stage Coach House, undated (Box-folder 12/10)
      - Salem, undated (Box-folder 12/11)
        Includes home of E. N. Cook, Court House, and Old State Capitol.
      - Silverton, undated (Box-folder 12/12)
        Includes home of Homer Davenport and the Parkersville Hotel.
      - Scotts Valley - John Letsom home, undated (Box-folder 12/13)
      - St. Louis - Catholic church, undated (Box-folder 12/14)
      - St. Paul - Catholic church, undated (Box-folder 12/15)
      - Wolf Creek Tavern, undated (Box-folder 12/16)
      - Yoncalla - Charles Applegate home, undated (Box-folder 12/17)
    - Washington
      - Mary's Corner - John R. Jackson home, undated (Box-folder 12/18)
      - Vancouver - Hudson Bay Apple Tree, undated (Box-folder 12/19)
- Pictorial Oregon: Twenty-Four Memorable Photographs by Walter Boychuk, 1941; Group 4 (Box-folder 10/49)
  Printed booklet of photomechanical prints of Boychuk's photographs, edited by Harry Bigelow Coffin and published by Beattie & Hoffman (Portland, Or.).
- "Pacific Northwest by Boychuk" photograph album, undated; Group 5 (Box 13)
  Bound album of photographs taken by Boychuk, annotated with his titles and negative numbers.